**Privacy Policy**
==================

**This Privacy Policy was last updated on March 23rd, 2021**
------------------------------------------------------------

This privacy policy (“Policy”) describes how the personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) you may provide on the interviewstream.com, rivs.com, hirebar.com, “interviewstream” mobile application, and any of their related products and services (collectively, “Services”) is collected, protected and used. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your Personal Information and how you can access and update this information. This Policy is a legally binding agreement between you (“User”, “you” or “your”) and interviewstream, Inc. (“interviewstream, Inc.”, “we”, “us” or “our”) and its subsidiaries (Thrive, and InterviewGuide Builder). By accessing and using the Services, you acknowledge that you have read, understood, and agree to be bound by the terms of this Policy. This Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control, or to individuals that we do not employ or manage.

**Automatic collection of information**
---------------------------------------

When you open the Website or use the Mobile Application, our servers automatically record information that your browser or device sends. This data may include information such as your device’s IP address and location, browser, and device name and version, operating system type and version, language preferences, the webpage you were visiting before you came to the Services, pages of the Services that you visit, the time spent on those pages, the information you search for on the Services, access times and dates, and other statistics.

Information collected automatically is used only to identify potential cases of abuse and establish statistical information regarding the usage and traffic of the Services. This statistical information is not otherwise aggregated in such a way that would identify any particular user of the system.

**Collection of personal information**
--------------------------------------

In order to become a registered user of the Services, interviewstream requires you to create a user account. To register for a user account, you must provide the following personally identifiable information:

* If you are an employer, you must provide your company’s name and e-mail address of a contact at your company.
* If you are an employee of an employer, you must provide your name, e-mail address, and phone.
* If you are a jobseeker, the information that you need to provide is determined by the employer who is using interviewstream to review candidates for their job opening or similar opportunity.

When required, this information may include the following:

* Personal details such as name, country of residence, etc.
* Contact information such as email address, address, etc.
* Account details such as user name, unique user ID, password, etc.
* Geolocation data such as latitude and longitude.

**Use and processing of collected information**
-----------------------------------------------

In order to make the Services available to you, or to meet a legal obligation, we may need to collect and use certain Personal Information. If you do not provide the information that we request, we may not be able to provide you with the requested products or services. Any of the information we collect from you may be used for the following purposes:

* Create and manage user accounts
* Deliver products or services
* Improve products and services
* Respond to inquiries and offer support
* Request user feedback
* Improve the user experience
* Run and operate the Services

Processing your Personal Information depends on how you interact with the Services, where you are located in the world and if one of the following applies: (i) you have given your consent for one or more specific purposes; this, however, does not apply, whenever the processing of Personal Information is subject to California Consumer Privacy Act or European data protection law; (ii) provision of information is necessary for the performance of an agreement with you and/or for any pre-contractual obligations thereof; (iii) processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which you are subject; (iv) processing is related to a task that is carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of official authority vested in us; (v) processing is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by us or by a third party.

Note that under some legislations we may be allowed to process information until you object to such processing (by opting out), without having to rely on consent or any other of the following legal bases below. In any case, we will be happy to clarify the specific legal basis that applies to the processing, and in particular whether the provision of Personal Information is a statutory or contractual requirement, or a requirement necessary to enter into a contract.

**Managing information**
------------------------

You are able to delete certain Personal Information we have about you. The Personal Information you can delete may change as the Services change. When you delete Personal Information, however, we may maintain a copy of the unrevised Personal Information in our records for the duration necessary to comply with our obligations to our affiliates and partners, and for the purposes described below.

**Disclosure of information**
-----------------------------

Depending on the requested Services or as necessary to complete any transaction or provide any service you have requested, we may share your information with your consent with our trusted third parties that work with us, any other affiliates and subsidiaries we rely upon to assist in the operation of the Services available to you. We do not share Personal Information with unaffiliated third parties. These service providers are not authorized to use or disclose your information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or comply with legal requirements. We may share your Personal Information for these purposes only with third parties whose privacy policies are consistent with ours or who agree to abide by our policies with respect to Personal Information. These third parties are given Personal Information they need only in order to perform their designated functions, and we do not authorize them to use or disclose Personal Information for their own marketing or other purposes.

We will disclose any Personal Information we collect, use or receive if required or permitted by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process, and when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.

In the event we go through a business transition, such as a merger or acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your user account, and Personal Information will likely be among the assets transferred.

**Retention of information**
----------------------------

We will retain and use your Personal Information for the period necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law. We may use any aggregated data derived from or incorporating your Personal Information after you update or delete it, but not in a manner that would identify you personally. Once the retention period expires, Personal Information shall be deleted. Therefore, the right to access, the right to erasure, the right to rectification and the right to data portability cannot be enforced after the expiration of the retention period.

**Transfer of information**
---------------------------

Depending on your location, data transfers may involve transferring and storing your information in a country other than your own. You are entitled to learn about the legal basis of information transfers to a country outside the European Union or to any international organization governed by public international law or set up by two or more countries, such as the UN, and about the security measures taken by us to safeguard your information. If any such transfer takes place, you can find out more by checking the relevant sections of this Policy or inquire with us using the information provided in the contact section.

**Choice and access to data controlled by our customers**
---------------------------------------------------------

interviewstream has no direct relationship with the individual employees and job-seekers whose personal data it processes on our behalf of our customers. Individuals applying or interviewing for jobs with employers that are interviewstream customers are identified by their email address that associates all applications and interviews for that individual with that email address. The individual can access their My Interviews page at the Site and transmit requests to the employers to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data in an application. The employer is responsible for complying with the individual’s request. If requested to remove data we will respond within a reasonable timeframe. interviewstream retains an archive copy of the individual’s personal data we process on behalf of our Customers for as long as needed to provide services to our Customer and as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. Additionally, if you are an employee or job-seeker and would no longer like to be contacted by a particular employer or employers, please contact them directly to resolve your concern.

**The rights of users**
-----------------------

You may exercise certain rights regarding your information processed by us. In particular, you have the right to do the following: (i) you have the right to withdraw consent where you have previously given your consent to the processing of your information; (ii) you have the right to object to the processing of your information if the processing is carried out on a legal basis other than consent; (iii) you have the right to learn if information is being processed by us, obtain disclosure regarding certain aspects of the processing and obtain a copy of the information undergoing processing; (iv) you have the right to verify the accuracy of your information and ask for it to be updated or corrected; (v) you have the right, under certain circumstances, to restrict the processing of your information, in which case, we will not process your information for any purpose other than storing it; (vi) you have the right, under certain circumstances, to obtain the erasure of your Personal Information from us; (vii) you have the right to receive your information in a structured, commonly used and machine readable format and, if technically feasible, to have it transmitted to another controller without any hindrance. This provision is applicable provided that your information is processed by automated means and that the processing is based on your consent, on a contract which you are part of or on pre-contractual obligations thereof.

**The right to object to processing**
-------------------------------------

Where Personal Information is processed for the public interest, in the exercise of an official authority vested in us or for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by us, you may object to such processing by providing a ground related to your particular situation to justify the objection.

**Data protection rights under GDPR**
-------------------------------------

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights and interviewstream, Inc. aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Information. If you wish to be informed what Personal Information we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us. In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:

* You have the right to request access to your Personal Information that we store and have the ability to access your Personal Information.
* You have the right to request that we correct any Personal Information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request us to complete the Personal Information you believe is incomplete.
* You have the right to request the erase your Personal Information under certain conditions of this Policy.
* You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Information.
* You have the right to seek restrictions on the processing of your Personal Information. When you restrict the processing of your Personal Information, we may store it but will not process it further.
* You have the right to be provided with a copy of the information we have on you in a structured, machine-readable and commonly used format.
* You also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where interviewstream, Inc. relied on your consent to process your Personal Information

You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our collection and use of your Personal Information. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority in the European Economic Area (EEA).

**U.S-E.U. Privacy Shield**
---------------------------

interviewstream complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Frameworks, as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union and Switzerland to the United States. interviewstream has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit https://www.privacyshield.gov/.

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, interviewstream commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. EU and Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact interviewstream at privacy@interviewstream.com

interviewstream has further committed to refer unresolved Privacy Shield complaints to JAMS, an alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint from us, or if we have not addressed your complaint to your satisfaction, please contact or visit https://www.jamsadr.com for more information or to file a complaint. The services of JAMS are provided at no cost to you.

**California privacy rights**
-----------------------------

In addition to the rights as explained in this Policy, California residents who provide Personal Information (as defined in the statute) to obtain products or services for personal, family, or household use are entitled to request and obtain from us, once a calendar year, information about the Personal Information we shared, if any, with other businesses for marketing uses. If applicable, this information would include the categories of Personal Information and the names and addresses of those businesses with which we shared such personal information for the immediately prior calendar year (e.g., requests made in the current year will receive information about the prior year). To obtain this information please contact us.

**Canada privacy rights**
-------------------------

If you are a resident of Canada, you have certain data protection rights and interviewstream, Inc. aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Information. If you wish to be informed what Personal Information we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us.

**How to exercise these rights**
--------------------------------

Any requests to exercise your rights can be directed to interviewstream, Inc. through the contact details provided in this document. Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests. Your request must provide sufficient information that allows us to verify that you are the person you are claiming to be or that you are the authorized representative of such person. You must include sufficient details to allow us to properly understand the request and respond to it. We cannot respond to your request or provide you with Personal Information unless we first verify your identity or authority to make such a request and confirm that the Personal Information relates to you.

**Privacy of children**
-----------------------

We do not knowingly collect any Personal Information from children under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18, please do not submit any Personal Information through the Services. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to help enforce this Policy by instructing their children never to provide Personal Information through the Services without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 18 has provided Personal Information to us through the Services, please contact us. You must also be at least 16 years of age to consent to the processing of your Personal Information in your country (in some countries we may allow your parent or guardian to do so on your behalf).

**Cookies**
-----------

The Services use “cookies” to help personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a webpage server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

We may use cookies to collect, store, and track information for statistical purposes to operate the Services. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the features of the Services. Click here to learn more about cookies and how they work.

**Do Not Track signals**
------------------------

Some browsers incorporate a Do Not Track feature that signals to websites you visit that you do not want to have your online activity tracked. Tracking is not the same as using or collecting information in connection with a website. For these purposes, tracking refers to collecting personally identifiable information from consumers who use or visit a website or online service as they move across different websites over time. How browsers communicate the Do Not Track signal is not yet uniform. As a result, the Services are not yet set up to interpret or respond to Do Not Track signals communicated by your browser. Even so, as described in more detail throughout this Policy, we limit our use and collection of your personal information.

**Links to other resources**
----------------------------

The Site may provide links to third party websites or resources not associated with interviewstream, and over which interviewstream does not have control (“External Websites”). Such links do not constitute an endorsement by interviewstream of the External Websites, the content displayed therein, or the persons or entities associated therewith. You acknowledge that interviewstream is only providing these links as a convenience, and you agree that interviewstream is not responsible for the content of such External Websites. Your use of External Websites is subject to the respective terms of use and privacy policies located on the linked to External Websites. interviewstream does not store any information (user name, password) used to access these External Websites.

**Our Blog**
------------

Our Website offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personally identifiable information from our blog or community forum, contact us at privacy@interviewstream.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personally identifiable information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

**Testimonials**
----------------

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at support@interviewstream.com.

**Other social media features and web-apps**
--------------------------------------------

Our Website includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button, Google+ button, Twitter and Linkedin Share button. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

**Information security**
------------------------

We secure information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. We maintain reasonable administrative, technical, and physical safeguards in an effort to protect against unauthorized access, use, modification, and disclosure of Personal Information in its control and custody. However, no data transmission over the Internet or wireless network can be guaranteed. Therefore, while we strive to protect your Personal Information, you acknowledge that (i) there are security and privacy limitations of the Internet which are beyond our control; (ii) the security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and the Services cannot be guaranteed; and (iii) any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit by a third party, despite best efforts.

**Data breach**
---------------

In the event we become aware that the security of the Services has been compromised or users Personal Information has been disclosed to unrelated third parties as a result of external activity, including, but not limited to, security attacks or fraud, we reserve the right to take reasonably appropriate measures, including, but not limited to, investigation and reporting, as well as notification to and cooperation with law enforcement authorities. In the event of a data breach, we will make reasonable efforts to notify affected individuals if we believe that there is a reasonable risk of harm to the user as a result of the breach or if notice is otherwise required by law. When we do, we will post a notice on the Services, send you an email, mail you a letter.

**Changes and amendments**
--------------------------

We reserve the right to modify this Policy or its terms relating to the Services from time to time in our discretion and will notify you of any material changes to the way in which we treat Personal Information. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We may also provide notice to you in other ways in our discretion, such as through contact information you have provided. Any updated version of this Policy will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised Policy unless otherwise specified. Your continued use of the Services after the effective date of the revised Policy (or such other act specified at that time) will constitute your consent to those changes. However, we will not, without your consent, use your Personal Information in a manner materially different than what was stated at the time your Personal Information was collected.

**Acceptance of this policy**
-----------------------------

You acknowledge that you have read this Policy and agree to all its terms and conditions. By accessing and using the Services you agree to be bound by this Policy. If you do not agree to abide by the terms of this Policy, you are not authorized to access or use the Services.

**Contacting us**
-----------------

If you would like to contact us to understand more about this Policy or wish to contact us concerning any matter relating to individual rights and your Personal Information, you may do so via the support portal.

This document was last updated on March 23, 2021.

### About

interviewstream is dedicated to the success of more than 900 clients from K-12 school districts, emerging businesses, midsize companies, large enterprises, colleges, and universities.

### Solutions

### Privacy

### Contact

877-773-3164 (USA Only)  

### Follow

© 2024 interviewstream | all rights reserved [XML Sitemap](https://interviewstream.com/sitemap_index.xml)
